ALI PAJAND

ali.pajand@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/alipajand/ @ alipajand.com/en

Senior Frontend Developer

Summary

I'm an extroverted, energetic, highly positive and hardworking developer with +8 years expertises in web development (frontend) with a history of graphics knowledge.

My main affection is to learn about web and new technologies from various sources. I enjoy encountering challenges for which my problem solving ability manifests and expands. I love to see beautiful codes that have an adherence to standards and open-source solutions. I try to figure out all possible solutions but then act based on best practices and standard ways.

View my latest noticeable projects: @alipajand

Email me: hello@alipajand.com - ali.pajand@gmail.com

Work Experience

Mar 2018 - Present

Senior Frontend Developer

Ctrl+Tech

- Implement websites and admin panels for: (You can find me on each project:
 - SITE_URL/humans.txt)
 - https://tazebar.com
 - https://ctrltech.comhttps://admartiz.com
 - https://banikar.com
 - https://techtoman.com
 - https://bidzila.com
 - https://firouzehPlat.com
 - https://raad.com (Not Published)
 - https://advva.com (Not Published)
- Implement PWA for some of application
- Implement attractive online chat based on vue js
- Implement custom service worker
- Work with Firebase messaging

Jan 2014 - Dec 2017

Frontend Developer

Rayvarz Software Engineering

- Working in BPMS team (business process management system to rewrite online admin panel and portal in vuejs)
- Design pattern mentoring, UI Discussion and prepare prototype for programmers
- Working in BPMS team as frontend developer (business process management system to rewrite online admin panel and portal in Vue.js)
- Collaborate on service catalogue for Ministry of Economic Affairs of Iran
- Change user interface of eOffice to create new sense and change admin panel arguments and texts
- Maintenance of old eOffice application and add feature
- Start to implement new website version of rayvarz
- Try to integrate UI of all products in whole company

Jun 2013 - Sep 2013	Internship Frontend Developer
---------------------	-------------------------------

Unilever (Iran Department)

• Help to develop and maintain the global application

Remote Experiences

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021 Senior Frontend Developer (San Francisco, US)

Galliot

Implement neuralet (own website) and its admin panel in nuxt js framework in vuejs

Implement adaptive learning admin panel and its landing page in vuejs cli

July 2021 - Sep 2021 Senior Frontend Developer (Oslo, Norway)

Bird Flocks

Impletent main panel with next js framework in reactjs as a single project

Apr 2019 - Jul 2019 Frontend Developer (Vancouver, Canada)

Timely

Help to develop and maintain the global application in angularjs

Jan 2015 - Jan 2017 Frontend Developer (Lahti, Finland)

Lahtiprecision

Implementing three generation of website in these years

Education

Sep 2014 - Aug 2018 M.Sc. Computer/Information Technology Administration

Allame Tabataba'i University

Thesis: Identification of Factors to Use Cloud Computing by University Students in Educational

Process

Sep 2010 - Aug 2014 B.Sc. Engineering/Industrial Management

Allame Tabataba'i University

Skills

Vue js | Nuxt js

- Pure version and **Nuxt** as ssr framework
- **Vuex** as State management tools
- Familiar with **Typescript**

React Native

• With **Typescript**

Notifications and Service Workers

• Onesignal & Google Firebase

React is | Next is | Gatsby

- Pure version and **Next** as ssr framework
- Redux as State management tools
- Familiar with **Typescript**

Unit Tests

• BDD and TDD tests with **Jest**, **Mocha** and **E2E**

Progressive Web Apps (PWA)

Workbox

Version Contro	ller

Python (Django) & Nodejs

Git, SVN and TFS

• Familiar as a backend background and web api

Created with 🔽 VisualCV